Hello everyone and welcome back to the new
video, I am your friend Nikhil,
with another new video, and
as I told you, all my recent videos will be
seen in this T-shirt because today I am
sitting inside the car, today the temperature is 2 degrees
less, so it is 41 instead of 43, that's why
I came and sat in the car and am
making a video for you, okay, so
you have seen this video
about Ekko Insurance, if you
drive a car, you should take Ekko Insurance or
not, I will tell you this in the video,
stay till the end of the video, if you liked it then
definitely give it a like and don't forget to
subscribe to the channel and hit the notification
bell, let's get going
[Music] First of all,
tell me who among you uses Ekko Insurance or is thinking of using it, and this is
not a sponsored video, guys, it's just that I feel it's
my responsibility to share my
experience with you all, to tell you what I have seen
in claim settlement from my eyes  Did you
face any problems or not, how well it went or
not, tell me that, so
first of all you tell me
which insurance do you use, which one do
you like best and whether you use it or
not, tell me, not springs again,
okay, so last September after a lot of thinking,
you know, I went with Coco Insurance,
obviously its premium is low,
many people refused saying what will happen to its
settlement, it will not happen, this that,
I said friend, let it go, we will see, let's take Coco, I don't know
what I was thinking, but it's
okay, it was making a
difference of Rs. 00
in the overall insurance premium, so I went with that, to be very
honest, if you drive the car carefully, then there is
no need for insurance,
it is just a protection and it is a very important protection,
to have insurance is very very
important, so
anyway, if you have seen my videos, then the
front right bumper and fender of my car,
when I was parking the car once  It was
worn out in my garage but
I haven't got it repaired yet, I
said it's okay, some stains are good, I
told you the video is on the i-link, you can watch it, it's
here or there, it's in one place, watch that video, a
lot of people have seen it and also
given love to that video, thank you so much for that guys,
so I was thinking what to do, what to do,
but recently what happened in my car,
you have seen that service
video, there was so much problem, so
I finally did some rusting on the car,
you know the paint quality, there was
rusting on the car, so I
gave my car and when I said that when the resting is getting
fixed, then the left fender here would
also be repaired, so I
called Ko, so when I called Ko, let's
tell you what happens at the end of the video, they passed it,
no, let's tell you at the end of the video, so
I called Ko to ask, Bhaiya,
I want to give my car in claim,
their response is very good, you will call, you
call very nicely  Yes, they don't have
any physical stores but they are very
responsive online. Excellent appreciator.
So he said, Sir, if
you get the work done at our workshop, you will have to pay only Rs. 2000 as
deductible. The
rest they will take care of
in the claim. I said, okay, but
this is an EV, the question is the same, will
you be able to repair an EV and if there is any problem,
my warranty gets lapsed, then
who will guarantee it? He said, that's correct,
and Les Motors, where my car was taken, was
not in their list, according to their
policy, in that case the service center is not
listed with one, they will pass the claim, it will
not be
cashless, there will be a deductible of Rs. 5000
plus Rs. 2000, so Rs. 7000 in total, and it will be
cashless. They will coordinate and
give me the money and then I will have to pay the service center.
Hearing this, my mind went blank for a second,
I said  Dude, I got trapped, it had never happened
before, it always happens in cashless transactions, so this had
not happened, my mind was really
shaken, guys, so I told them
that if you can do it then get it done at your
service centre, but my warranty should not lapse, they
said sir, look, it depends,
if there is a fender, then will the
warranty lapse because of the fender, will they open the fender,
repair it, and install it, I said do
whatever you want, my warranty should not lapse, then
they thought, then said,
okay wait, let's discuss something among the
sales and they said, no problem,
you go to your authorized service centre,
we will talk to them and understand the estimate, you will
not have to deduct Rs. 000, you will have to deduct only Rs. 2000 which is
normal, which they charge everyone,
so thank you, everyone, I am skeptical, should you
take COCO or
not, this experience is important for you,
they themselves follow up very well,
you do not have to follow up, net net,
I am happy with it  I was so much worried that I am
taking my health insurance to them, I was so worried that
I am taking my health
insurance also to them, they
spoke to the service centre, they gave an
estimator that no brother, we will not pay for both sides, we will pay
for one side only, fair enough,
whatever came, they sent me a proper bill
that brother, the bill is of 11000 in front of your screen,
I am giving it to you, the bill is of 11000, the
rest they will deposit the money in my account
and I have to pay within
five minutes, I accepted the
money in my account, they said five minutes extra
but within half an hour the entire
case ended there itself, they transferred the money to my account,
now I will only take the car from the TA people, I will make the
full payment to them and come back, the
experience was amazing with Coco,
obviously initially there was a little skepticism,
so I was not able to understand what is right and what is
wrong, how will it happen, will they give the claim or not, whether they will allow it or not, only that
The thing is that it will
not be cashless there but the money will come in your account,
you just make the payment, the thing is the same, it is
cashless, isn't it? So
I thought of making this small video for you, friend, I am
using yours, so should you use it or
not, I am fine, I am very happy, I will
use it, I will renew it from them only, so
much so I am taking my health policy from them only, I am very happy with it,
you can take your decision yourself, you
can use this video as a reference, that
was the purpose of bringing it to you, so if you liked the video then give it
a like,
please tell me in the comment section and I will meet
you very soon in the next video, till then take care,
God bless, I love you always.